

Thanawit Kaniwaranon

DEVELOPER

CONTACT ME

(+66)97-075-5663kt.thanawit@gmail.com thanawit-k.github.io/profile

EDUCATION

2020 - 2022 : King Mongkut's University of Technology Thonburi

Master of Science in Digital Business Information System

GPAX: 3.35

2014 - 2018Kasetsart University Kamphaeng Saen Campus

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

GPAX: 2.65

SKILLS

Vue.is

Bootstrap

¡Query

JavaScript

• PHP

Node.js

NestJS

Spring Boot

ABOUT ME

I am a software developer proficient in JavaScript and Vue Framework, with experience working in teams and as an independent worker. I am able to learn and adapt to new technologies and am ready to collaborate with your team to develop better software for the future.

WORK EXPERIENCES

COREWISDOM Co., Ltd. 2022 - Present **Programmer Analyst**

- Analyzed user requirements, developed

understanding of functionality needed in software systems by working closely with clients.

Designed and developed efficient software solutions using programming languages and software development tools.

- Maintained and upgraded software systems to ensure efficiency and effectiveness for clients.

2018 - 2022 Front-end Developer

> - Designed and developed responsive web pages and user interfaces using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

> - Optimized website performance and load times

through code optimization

- Maintain and update existing web pages and user interfaces to ensure they are compatible

across multiple platforms.